joshhosler.biz 2012-01-17

# Privacy Policy

This site is part owned and operated by Josh Hosler (“Owner”). Owner does not pass personally identifiable information of our users to DoubleClick or other third-party advertising companies.

Owner takes your privacy very seriously. Because of this, it wants to provide you with information on how it collects, gathers and identifies information during your visit to [www.joshhosler.biz](http://www.joshhosler.biz/) (the “Site”). This information may be expanded or updated as it changes or develops the Site. For this reason, we recommend that you review this policy from time to time to see if anything has changed. Your continued use of our site signifies your acceptance of the latest privacy policy.

**Personally Identifiable Information** refers to information that tells specifically who you are, such as your name, phone number, email or postal address. In many cases this information is needed to provide the personalized or enhanced service that you have requested. The amount of Personally Identifiable Information that you choose to disclose is completely up to you. The only way to know something about you personally is if you provide it to in conjunction with one of the Site’s services.

**What information is collected and how is it used?**

The Site collects information on its users in three ways: by your voluntary submissions (for instance, if you sign up for an email newsletter) and/or surveys; sweepstakes and/or contest entries; and through cookie technology.

In an effort to provide personalization and opportunities for prizes and services, we may at times ask you to submit information such as your name or email address, or to share your interests and hobbies with us. You never have to answer these questions, and you can decline this exchange of information on any site on the Internet - not just ours - at any time. However, if you choose to withhold requested information, we may not be able to provide you with some of the services dependent upon the collection of this information, such as a personalized stock portfolio, a sweepstakes entry, or the purchase and shipment of products and prizes to people who visit our network.

The information we collect is used in a variety of ways: for internal review; to improve the content of the site, thus making your user experience more valuable; to notify you about updates to the service; and to let you know about products and services that you may be interested in.

**Email:** If you have provided us your email address, we may periodically send promotional emails to its subscribers about services offered by us and associated companies. If you do not wish to receive email information from us, please let us know by emailing us at: [josh.hosler@gmail.com](mailto:josh.hosler@gmail.com). The "email this article" feature is an easy way for you to send articles through email. The email addresses that you supply to use this service will not be used for any other purpose without your consent. 

**With whom do we share the information we gather or tracks?**

From time to time we share this information with other reputable organizations for marketing purposes or the information is used to contact consumers for its own marketing endeavors. As a valued consumer, we offer you the opportunity to “opt out,” or request not to accept these marketing opportunities. If at any time you change your mind and do not want to share your email address or home address with other companies and/or organizations, or would simply like to be removed from the list, please let us know by emailing us at: [josh.hosler@gmail.com](mailto:josh.hosler@gmail.com).

**Cookies**

We may automatically collect non-personally identifiable information and data through the use of “cookies.” Cookies are small text files a Web site uses to recognize repeat users, facilitate the user's ongoing access to the site and facilitate the use of the site. Cookies also allow a site to track usage behavior and compile site usage information that will allow for the improvement of content and target advertising.

The Site may use DoubleClick and other third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit the Site. These companies may use non-personally identifiable information (i.e. not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements on this site and other sites about goods and services that may be of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, click here [ www.doubleclick.net/naiprivacy](http://www.doubleclick.net/naiprivacy).

The Site may also use a third party to collect non-personally identifiable information using web beacons. Click here: [josh.hosler@gmail.com](mailto:josh.hosler@gmail.com) to learn more about how we use a third party service to collect and use information on these sites.

**About Children's Privacy**

The Site is committed to the safety of children. Children under 18 may not participate in any sweepstakes or contests on the Site. Also, we encourage children under the age of 18 to ask a parent for permission before providing or sending any information to anyone online.

**Your Consent**

By using the Site, you consent to the collection and use of the information described in this Privacy Policy. Once again, if you do not wish us to share this information with other reputable companies that we think you might be interested in, please let us know by emailing us at [josh.hosler@gmail.com](mailto:josh.hosler@gmail.com).

**Questions?**

We welcome your questions and/or comments. Please send all queries to [josh.hosler@gmail.com](mailto:josh.hosler@gmail.com).
